pinkblushmaternity.com 2019-12-16

# PinkBlush Maternity Privacy Statement

##### Privacy and Security

PinkBlush ("Company" or "We") respects your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.pinkblushmaternity.com (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. This policy applies to information we collect: 

  * On this Website.
  * In email, text, phone calls, postal mail, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by: 

  * Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

###### Children Under the Age of 18

Our Website is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age of 18 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this Website or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at [support@shoppinkblush.com](mailto:support@shoppinkblush.com).

###### Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("personal information");
  * That is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners Google, Facebook, Bing, Yahoo, Sidecar, SteelHouse, Attentive, Talkable, Pepperjam Affiliates, Pinterest, Reddit, Dynamic Yield, Zendesk, Zinrelo, Searchspring, Hotjar, TurnTo, Stripe, Paypal, Amazon, eShopWorld, and Afterpay.

###### Information You Provide To Us

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence, if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
  * Your search queries on the Website.
  * You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages/you may set certain privacy settings for such information by logging into your account profile, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions.

###### Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). Some browsers have a "do not track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. At this time, we do not respond to browser "do not track" signals.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information, or may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information. 
  * Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website [and our e-mails] may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

###### Third-Party Use of Cookies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information on targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information. 

###### How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * To personalize your website experience (e.g. the content and information that we may send or display to you).
  * For marketing and promotional purposes (e.g. to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions). We also may use the information that we learn about you to assist us in advertising on third party websites.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties’ goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information. We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

###### Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of PinkBlush's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by PinkBlush about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information. 
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use www.pinkblushmaternity.com/t-pbm-termsofuse.aspx and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of PinkBlush, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

###### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. We may disclose your Information over time and to other affiliate websites to third parties for promotional purposes. We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see or go to <https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa> for more information
  * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your email address/contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile, by following the removal instructions in the communication that you receive, or by sending us an email stating your request to [support@shoppinkblush.com](mailto:support@shoppinkblush.com). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.
  * Targeted Advertising. California residents may have additional personal data rights and choices. Please see or go to <https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa> for more information.

###### Accessing and Collecting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. You may also send us an email at [support@shoppinkblush.com](mailto:support@shoppinkblush.com) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our Terms of Use. California residents may have additional personal information rights and choices. Please see Your California Privacy Rights for more information. 

###### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit https://www.oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa. California’s “Shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [support@shoppinkblush.com](mailto:support@shoppinkblush.com).

###### Your GDPR Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the European Union (E.U. or “EU”), EU law may provide you with certain rights regarding our use of your personal information or personal data. To learn more about your EU privacy rights in connection with the GDPR (the General Data Protection Regulation of the E.U.), visit <http://data.europa.eu/eli/reg/20156/679/2016-05-04>. PinkBlush's contact details are below, see Contact Us. PinkBlush's Data Protection Officer (DPO) can be reached at: Attn: Data Protection Officer, PinkBlush, 75 Doppler, Suite 200, Irvine, California 92618 or by email address at [support@shoppinkblush.com](mailto:support@shoppinkblush.com). 

PinkBlush uses cookies to improve user and customer experience and to provide a more efficient communication of new products and sales. For more information on cookies, the categories and sources of personal data which may be collected by us or third parties, and how it relates to your personal data, please see Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It, Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies, Third-Party Use of Cookies, How We Use Your Information, Disclosure Of Your Information, and Choices About How We Use And Disclose Your Information.

PinkBlush may process your personal data: to complete a financial and/or contractual obligation for a sale of goods or services; via your our opt-in consent; when you participate in any activity on the Website or Website’s affiliates; to verify your identity when applicable, such as, but not limited to, if and when you log in or logged in to your account with the Website; as a fulfillment of Website’s Terms of Use; and/or other circumstances subject to the laws of applicable jurisdictions. If certain personal data is not collected or processed, PinkBlush may not be able to improve user experience on the Website, create a more efficient communication with users, provide updates to new goods or sales to users and potential users, and other related activities to providing a better and more user friendly Website.

The legal grounds for which PinkBlush may process your personal data may be based on your consent (opt-in via Email, Website, Social Media platform(s)), contract obligation (financial transaction), legal obligation (government agency or court request), or legitimate interests (verify identity; investigate fraud; improve user experience; and other legitimate interest that may arise). 

PinkBlush does not sell or share your personal data with any third party not affiliated with PinkBlush.

You have the right of access, correction, erasure, restriction, objection, and data portability in connection to your personal data. You have the right to withdraw consent and how to exercise that right if the organization uses consent justify data processing. You have the right to make a complaint with the applicable local data protection authority and how to exercise that right. Do not use or visit the Website if you do not agree with any of the policies regarding your privacy/personal data and with the Website’s Terms of Use.

###### Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

###### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the primary email address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

###### Contact Info

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [support@shoppinkblush.com](mailto:support@shoppinkblush.com). 

Last Updated On: November 6, 2019
